[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Different colors derive form the different wavelengths of the spectrum of light. What part of it do we call visible light, i.e. we can perceive with our eyes?", "correct_answer": "380 - 740 nm", "incorrect_answers": ["0 - 500 nm", "1000 + nm", "700 - 900 nm"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the fate of John Dillinger in the 2009 movie Public Enemies?", "correct_answer": "He is shot dead.", "incorrect_answers": ["He breaks his girlfriend out of jail and they get married.", "He manages to escape from the FBI and becomes an honest man.", "He commits suicide before the FBI agents could arrest him."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many items are there in a a Bakers Dozen?", "correct_answer": "13", "incorrect_answers": ["15", "12", "None of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This moon is the most volcanic object in the solar system. Its volcanoes erupt sulfur, sulfur dioxide and silicate rock,  constantly resurfacing it.", "correct_answer": "Io", "incorrect_answers": ["Titania", "Ganymede", "Europa"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Aristotle believed these two scientific fields had nothing in common.", "correct_answer": "Mathematics and physics", "incorrect_answers": ["Zoology and human anatomy", "Geometry and arithmetic", "Philosophy and psychology"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The armor plates of pangolins are made of tough bone.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "There is a particular connection between birth stones and months.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which of these African environments are hyenas NOT found?", "correct_answer": "Desert", "incorrect_answers": ["Forests", "Mountains", "Grasslands"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Do white lions exsist in the wild?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these giraffe subspecies is easily distinguished by the very light colored spots on its body?", "correct_answer": "West African Giraffe", "incorrect_answers": ["All of these", "South African Giraffe", "Somali Giraffe"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the Yiddish word Bupkis mean in English?", "correct_answer": "Nothing", "incorrect_answers": ["None", "Never", "Rubbish"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The moon is not round, but egg shaped.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]